ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records 5619/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers Federation Correspondence, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  English, German. French
- International Textiles, Garment and Leather Workers Federation-3rd World Congress, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  J.P. Stevens discussion
- International Textiles, Garment and Leather Workers Federation-3rd World Congress-Pending, etc, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  Also IUD positions; Policy; Data; Proposals; Correspondence
- International Textiles, Garment and Leather Workers Federation-3rd World Congress-Elections(Nominations), 1980 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  German, French, English
- ITGLWF 3rd World Congress, Executives Committee and Congress Agenda, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 23)
- ITGLWF-3rd World Congress-ACTWU Report on Activities, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 24)
- IUD-Future Directions Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  Officer's report; News Articles
- ITGLWF-3rd World Congress, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  Misc Correspondence, Ballot listing in German, French, English
- ITGWF-3rd World Congress-Foreign Corporations Listings, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 27)
- ITGWLF-3rd World Congress-Jacob Sheinkman Address, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 28)
- ITGLWF-3rd World Congress-Materials from ITGLWF, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 29)
- IUD-Executive Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  Report in preparation for January 1980 meeting; "Digest" newsletter
- ITGLWF, 1979-1980 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  Agreements; Policy; Reports; Correspondence
- Italian Relief Fund-AFL-CIO, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  1980 Earthquake relief
- Boys Town of Italy, 1976-1980 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  Donation Records; Correspondence
- J miscellaneous, 1976-1980 (Box 73, Folder 34)
- Jewish Daily Forward, 1976-1980 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  Correspondence, Contains Yiddish Article
- Joint Boards-General, 1972-1979 (Box 73, Folder 36)
- Joint Board-Baltimore, 1975-1980 (Box 73, Folder 37)
  Correspondence, Research Reports
- Joint Boards-Biddeford-Saco/Lewiston Merger, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 38)
  Merger Agreement; Correspondence; Creation of Maine Joint Board
- Boston Joint Board, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 39)
  Audit Reports; Memos
- Joint Boards-Chicago and Central States Audits, 1971-1980 (Box 73, Folder 40)
- A miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- AG-Robert Abrams, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  Correspondence; Contributions to Reelection Campaign
- Administration Textile Program, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  Carter Administration?
- Administratorships, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  Correspondence; Reports; GEB resolutions
- Aetna Life and Casualty Insurance Co., 1981 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  Correspondence; Marketing Materials
- African American Labor Center, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Afro-Asian Institute-Hisadrut, 1981-1982 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  Correspondence; Meeting Minutes; Donation Records
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  November 1981; Memos; Legislative Packet
- AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  Also Reports; "American Banker" Newspaper
- AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Council Meeting-Amalgamated Bank resolution, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  February 1981
- AFL-CIO Conference-Maine, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  April 3, 1981
- AFL-CIO Committee on Public Education, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  Memos; Candidate endorsement lists
- AFL-CIO Secretary-Treasurer-(Conference and General Material, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  May Conference
- IUD-Correspondence, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  Resolutions; Reports; Policy Papers
- IUD-Correspondence, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  Memos; Articles; Reports
- IUD-Executive Council, 1982-1983 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  Memos regarding June 2, 1983 meeting
- IUD-Executive Council Meeting, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  January 12, Washington D.C. 1981. Meeting minutes; articles regarding; resolutions; reports
- IUD Executive Council Meeting, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  April 30-May 1, 1981. Minutes; Agenda; Reports; Memos
- IUD Executive Council Meeting, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  June 3/4 1982, Atlanta, GA. Schedule; Agenda; Reports; Memos
- IUD-Future Directions, 1980-1983 (Box 74, Folder 21)
- IUD Organizing, 1981-1982 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  Status reports; Memos; Newspaper Articles
- IUD Pension Fund Study-Research Drafts and Background info, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 23)
- IUD Pension Study-Action File, 1979-1982 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  Articles; Memos
- AFL-CIO-IUD: Trade Committee on International Trade Commission, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  Resolutions; Meetings lists; Reports
- IUD-Viewpoint Newsletter, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  Summer edition
- ACTWU & CMA Joint Technology Committee, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  Arbitration Records; Memos
- ACTWU-Committee on Organization, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  Meeting minutes; Organization results report.
- ACTWU-Regional Meeting Committee, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  May 25 Meeting Report
- Air Traffic Controller's Strike, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  Memos; Articles; Financial Reports
- Amalgamated Bank, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  Financial Records; Reports; Articles; Memos; Advertisements
- Amalgamated Bank, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  Reports, Memos, Financial Statements; other records
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  Investment Reports, Memos, Financial Statements, ETC
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industry Fund, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Department Store and Retail Employees Insurance Fund, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated department Store and Retail Employees Insurance Fund, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  Records; Memos
- Amalgamated Insurance-General Executive Board-Trustees, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  December meeting; Committee Lists, Finance Reports
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  Reports; Financial Records, Memos
- ALICO-Investment Committee, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  Documents regarding Martin-Segal
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Co., 1982 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company-Correspondence, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- UNA-Board of Governors, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  Memos; Agendas; Minutes
- UNA-Board of Governors, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  Meetings; Meetings; Agendas; Memos
- UNA-Economic Policy Council, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  Reports, Articles, Memos, Meetings, etc
- UNA-Finance and Budget Committee, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  December 1981 meeting
- Economic Policy Committee-Meeting, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  March 31, 1981
- UNA-EPC Migratory (Immigration) Panel, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  Memo; News Article; Report
- UNA-EPC Migratory (Immigration) Panel, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  Research; Reports; News Articles; Memos
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  Financial Records, Agendas, Memos
- UNA-EPC Productivity Panel, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- UNA-EPC Productivity Panel, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- UNA-EPC Productivity Panel [2 of 2], 1981 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  Reports-Fair Exchange; UAW Ford Employee Involvement; GTE Productivity
- UNA-EPC: Membership, 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Universal Microfilm Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  Promotional Materials, Memos; Finance records
- University of Pennsylvania, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  Article written by Jacob Sheinkman
- Urban Community Insurance Company, 1980-1981 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  Acquisition Report; Board of Directors meeting minutes; Annual Statements
- Urban Community Insurance Company, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  Proposals; Correspondence
- U.S. Trade Representative, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  Correspondence regarding Peru
- V Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  Correspondence; Retired Vice Presidents (Union)
- Victory Tours, 1977-1982 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  Correspondence regarding Travel Agency
- W Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Worker's Defense League, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  Anti-Slavery Efforts
- Workman's Circle Home, 1979-1982 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  Correspondence; Attorney General Report on Patient Deaths
- Workman's Circle Home-Luncheon, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  May 17, 1981, Honoring Lane Kirkland
- World Zionist Organization, 1979-1981 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  Correspondence, Donation Record
- Xerox Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Y Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  Articles; Polish Workers; Saudi Arabia report
- Z Miscellaneous, 1974-1981 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Zensen Domei, 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  Articles; Correspondence regarding Japanese imports
- ACTWU Committee on Organizing, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  Binder on activities, finances, correspondence, etc.
- P Miscellaneous, 1979-1982 (Box 77, Folder 19)
- Palm Beach Company, 1980-1982 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  Court Decision; Labor agreements; Articles; Correspondence
- Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 21)
- Pension Funds-Investments, 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  Correspondence, Proposed NYS legislation
- Phelps Stokes Fund [1 of 2], 1980-1982 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  Reports, Financial Statements, Agendas, Meeting Minutes, Articles
- Phelps Stokes Fund [2 of 2], 1980-1982 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  Member lists; Memos; Correspondence
- ACTWU-Political Action Committee, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 25)
- Progressive Alliance, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  Income and expense statements; Correspondence; Reports
- Public Relations, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 27)
- Pay Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Public Relations, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Queens College, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  Jacob Sheinkman Address, June
- R miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Ratner Corporation, 1980-1982 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, Settlement Agreement
- Research Department, 1981-1982 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Reunion of Old Timers, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  Information regarding; Charles Zimmerman Tribute
- Roundabout Theatre Company [1 of 2], 1981 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Roundabout Theatre Company [2 of 2], 1982 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- S Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Shearson/American Express (Dr. Robert Schwartz), 1981-1982 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Shoe Division, 1980-1982 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  Correspondence; Reports; Records
- Simon Scholarship Fund, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  Souvenir Journal
- Social Services Department, 1981-1982 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  Reports; Correspondence; "THREADS"
- Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  September 19, 1981, Washington D.C.
- "Solidarity", 1982 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  Newsletter, March 1982 edition
- Solomon & Rosenbaum, Dreschler& Leff, 1977-1982 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  Legal Correspondence
- Southern Department, 1981-1982 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  Memos regarding organizing efforts, others
- Southerners for Economic Justice, 1979-1982 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  Memos; Articles
- Szold and Brandwen, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- T Miscellaneous, 1979-1982 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  Memos; Correspondence; "Technology and Society" publication
- Tahari, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  Memos; Correspondence; Labor Agreement drafts
- Telluride Association, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  Directory of Associates, Correspondence between Jacob Sheinkman and Beatrice McLeod
- Textile-General Correspondence, 1975-1982 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  AFL-CIO/ACTWU agreement; Correspondence, etc.
- Textile Division Pension Fund., 1973-1981 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  1973 handbook, 1976 Operations report, 1981 correspondence
- Textile Staff Retirement Plan, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  Memos; Report
- Northeastern Massachusetts Joint Board, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  Resolution regarding Local merger
- Quin-State and NYS Regions, 1980-1981 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  Regional Director's reports-Joseph P. Coponi
- Trade Action File, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  Report of the President of the U.S. on Trade Agreements Program; Other reports
- Synthetic Fibers and Film Division, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  Correspondence; Memos
- U Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  Legislative amendments; Memos; Reports
- Union Label and Service Trades-Department of the State of New York, 1979-1981 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  Correspondence; Union Newsletter; Discussion of NYC railheads
- Unions Other then ACTWU, 1980-1982 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  Correspondence with
- United Automobile Workers, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 15)
- United Furniture Workers of America, 1979-1982 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  Correspondence; Memos; Press Release
- National Union of Hosiery and Knitwear Workers, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 17)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  Correspondence, Articles, ILGWU Ballot( Italian, Spanish, Chinese, Korean, Unknown Language)
- United Community Insurance Company, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  (Formerly Urban Community Insurance Company) Board Minutes; Correspondence, Biographical Info on Board of Directors
- United Housing Foundation, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 20)
- United Housing Foundation, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 21)
- United Nations Association-USA, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 22)
- United Nations Association-USA, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 23)
- H Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  Correspondence; Humanist Society
- Haggar Campaign, 1980-1982 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  Records of Organizing Campaign
- Hane's Worker's Voice, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  ACTWU newsletter/publication
- Hart, Shaffner and Marx, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  Annual Report, Correspondence
- ACTWU-Headwear Division, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  Financial Records; Labor Agreements; Correspondence; Reports
- Health Tex-Chesebrough-Ponds, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  Chesebrough-Pond's subsidy (?); News Articles; Memos; Reports
- Harry Herman Associates, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  "Labor's Stake in the New Mass Communication World" Report; Correspondence
- Sidney Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  Awards Programs; Memos: Audited Financial Statements; Memos
- Sidney Hillman Awards, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  Articles; Submissions
- Histadrut, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  Correspondence; Lebanon related documents; Jacob Sheinkman Address; Thomas Donahue award dinner
- Scott Hoyman, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  Oxford, New Jersey Local
- HUD, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  Memos and Articles regarding no-bid contracts
- Hughes and Hatcher, 1980-1982 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  Overview; Correspondence
- I Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Immigration-Illegal Aliens, 1981-1982 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  Articles; Reports; Legislative Discussion
- Imports-Special File, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  Memo
- Imports-Apparel, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  Report; Memos
- Imports-Shoes, 1979-1982 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  Correspondence; Memos; Reports; Press Releases
- Imports-General, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  Articles; Memos; Reports; Polls
- Imports, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  Documents and Correspondence regarding
- Indiana University of Pennsylvania, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, Honorary Degree
- Industrial Areas Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  Articles; Organizing information; Correspondence
- Industrial Department, 1978-1982 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- IAF Training Course, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  Memos regarding
- Institute for Policy Studies, 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Interco, Inc., 1980 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  Organizing records; Memos
- International Foundation of Employee Benefit plans, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  Correspondence, Report
- International Rescue Committee, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  Memos; News articles
- Italian-American Labor Council Meeting, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  December 11, 1982
- International Textile, Garment, and Leatherworker's Federation, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  Memos and Correspondence
- International Textile, Garment and Leatherworker's Union-Tokyo Convention, 1981-1982 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  1982 Convention, 1981 meeting minutes
- International Textile, Garment, and Leatherworker's Union-Africa Meeting, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 21)
- International Textile, Garment, and Leatherworker's Union, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 22)
- International Textile, Garment, & Leatherworker's Union-Presidium Meeting, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  New York, September 21-22
- Israel, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  U.S. Military sales To Saudi Arabia
- Boy's Town of Italy, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Italian-American Labor Council, 1980-1982 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  (Contains English, Italian) Dennis DeConcini and Lane Kirlland Luncheons; Memos; Italian Publications
- Italian Trip, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- J Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Jewish Affairs-General, 1980-1981 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- National Jewish Community Relations-Advisory Council, 1981-1982 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  Jewish USSR Emigration
- Jewish Daily Forward, 1981-1982 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- National Trade Union Council For Human Rights of the Jewish Labor Committee, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Johnson & Johnson, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  Company Overview, Memos; Articles
- Deep South Region, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  Bank Records
- Joint Boards-Eastern Shore, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Joint Board-Pennsylvania-Allen Ertel for Governor, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- Joint Board-West Coast Region, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  Spanish; English
- JTR Inc., 1982 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- JTR, Inc. [Folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- JTR, Inc. [Folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 81, Folder 19)
- JTR Conference-Philadelphia, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  March 27, 1981
- K Miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 81, Folder 21)
- The Kamber Group, 1981-1982 (Box 81, Folder 22)
- L Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 81, Folder 23)
- Labor Advisory Committee, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 24)
- Labor Policy Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 25)
- Labor Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Labor Council for Latin-American Advancement, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Labor Day Parade, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Labor Industrial Coalition for International Trade, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  Briefing Book
- Labor Unity Finder File, 1982-1983 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Laguardia Centennial-JS Labor Chairman, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- League of Woman Voters, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- M Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Mailing Department, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Mailgrams, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Manhattan Industries, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Memos, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Memos, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Man's Fashion Association of America, 1978-1981 (Box 82, Folder 16)
- Minimum Wage, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Robert J Moriarty, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Senator Patrick Moynihan, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Municipal Financial Union Leaders, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 20)
- Munsingwear, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  Agreement; Articles
- N Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  Various Correspondence
- NAACP Legal Defense Fund, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  Articles; Memos; Correspondence; Budgets
- National Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 24)
- National Coordinating Committee for Multi-employer Plans, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 25)
- National Immigration, Refugee & Citizenship Forum, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  Information regarding legislation
- National Institute for Voter Registration; Inc, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 27)
- National Planning Association, 1981-1982 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  Publications, Materials; Briefs; Memos; Correspondence
- NPA New American Realities Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- National Policy Exchange, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- National Urban League, 1980-1983 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Nation's Labor, 1978-1982 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  J.S.V. Publication/Digest
- HUD/Nazis, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  Articles and Correspondence regarding no-bid HUD sales; Nazi immigration
- New York State OSHA Environment Coalition, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- O Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Opelika MFG; Opelika; Alabama, 1981-1982 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  Company overview, Bargaining Settlement; Organizing Memos
- Organizing, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  Reports; Memos; Articles; Publications
- Organizing, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Organizing, 1978-1980 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- ACTWU Organizing Gains, 1979-1982 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- OSHA-Pam Woywod, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  HookerDurez OSHA violations
- OSHA Department, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  Memos; Reports; Articles
- OSHA. [Folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  July-December 1981
- OSHA. [Folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  January-June 1981
- NYS School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Life and Health Insurance Company, 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  Memos; Investments; Financial statements
- Amalgamated Special Benefits Association, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  June 8 Memo
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  Meeting Minutes; Reports
- Amalgamated Washable, Clothing, Sportswear and Allied Industries Fund., 1981--1982 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  Meeting Minutes; Reports; Financial records
- American Arts Alliance, 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  Agendas; Member lists; Reports; Correspondence; Articles
- American Immigration and Citizenship Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- American Income Life Insurance Company, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- American Income Life Insurance Company, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  Memos; 1980 Annual Report
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1980-1982 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- American ORT Federation, 1980-1982 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  (Organization for Rehabilitation Through Training)
- Americans For Democratic Action, 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  Reports; Memos
- Ampal-American Israel Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  Correspondence, April 1982 Board meeting
- Arrow Shirts, 1979-1982 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Asian American Free Labor Institute, 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1976-1982 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  Financial Statements; Reports; Memos
- Association for Labor Education, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- Atran Foundation, Inc, 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  USSR Jews experiences; Correspondence
- Auditing Department Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- Auditing Department Defense Fund, 1980-1982 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Auditing Department General Fund, 1980-1982 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  Financial Statements
- Auditing Department-Per Capita, 1980-1982 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  Financial Records
- Avtex Fibers, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 84, Folder 23)
- B miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers International Union, 1981-1982 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Bayly Corporation, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Bobbin Show, 1977-1981 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  Annual Convention
- (the) Bank Fur Gemeinwirtschaft, 1979-1982 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  German; English. Correspondence; Annual Report
- Botany Correspondence-General, 1979-1982 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Botany and McGregor Labels, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  Legal Documents; Correspondence
- Botto House, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  Newsletter, Correspondence
- British North American Committee. [Folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  July-December
- British North American Committee. [Folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  January-June
- British North American Committee. [Folder 1of 2], 1981 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- British North American Committee. [Folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- British North American Committee Meeting, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  December 4, 1981
- Bright of America, Inc, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Brookings Study (Box 85, Folder 15)
  Economic Policy Study